# Yong-chan Park

Ph.D. Student at Seoul National University

wjdakf3948@snu.ac.kr (+82)-2-880-7263

## **About Me**

I am a Ph.D. student majoring in Computer Science and Engineering at Seoul National University (SNU), advised by Prof. U Kang in Data Mining Laboratory. My research interests include machine learning and time series analysis. I am currently investigating a novel decomposition method for arrays, with a sequential analogy of Taylor's Theorem.

## **Research Interests**

Machine learning, Time series analysis, Anomaly detection

## **Education**

Ph.D. Student Mar. 2020 - Present

- Computer Science and Engineering, SNU

**Bachelor of Science** 

Mar. 2012 - Feb. 2019 - Department of Mathematical Sciences, SNU

# **Research Experiences**

#### A novel approach to Fourier Transform [1]

June 2020 - Present

- Propose Partial Fourier Transform (PFT) that rapidly computes a part of Fourier coefficients of a given time series and demonstrate the accuracy and efficacy of PFT on real-world anomaly detection [1]. PFT achieves 20x faster running time compared to SOTA algorithms.
- Patent pending

### **Stock movement prediction [2]**

Sep. 2020 - Present

- Propose Data-Axis Transformer with Multi-Level Contexts (DTML) for stock movement prediction that learns the correlations between stocks in an end-to-end way [2]. DTML achieves SOTA accuracy on six datasets collected from US, China, Japan, and UK.

#### Software development for patent management

Sep. 2020 - Present

- Implement LSH (Locality Sensitive Hashing) algorithm for finding similar patent data, and a BERT-based model for automatic patent classification.
- Develop a GUI with additional functionality of visualizing results.
- Industry-Academy Cooperation with Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering Co., Ltd.

# **Publications**

- [1] **Yong-chan Park**, Jun-Gi Jang, and U Kang. "Fast and Accurate Partial Fourier Transform for Time Series Data." KDD 2021
- [2] Jaemin Yoo, Yejun Soun, <u>Yong-chan Park</u>, and U Kang. "Accurate Multivariate Stock Movement Prediction via Data-Axis Transformer with Multi-Level Contexts." KDD 2021
- [3] <u>Yong-chan Park</u>\*, Sangjun Son\*, Minyong Cho, and U Kang. "DAO-CP: Data-Adaptive Online CP Decomposition for Tensor Stream." PLOS One 2022 (\*equal contribution)

# **Services**

Reviewer @ KDD 2022 Reviewer @ NeurIPS 2021